https://www.singlebrides.com/cms/privacy-statement

Privacy Statement
This privacy statement covers the site www.singlebrides.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment
to our user's privacy, it has made this privacy statement which is a disclosure of our information gathering and dissemination
practices for Single Brides.
What personally identifiable information Single Brides collects.
What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
What organization collects the information.
How Single Brides uses the information.
With whom Single Brides may share user information.
What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Single Brides control.
How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact Single Brides by email:
.
Information Collection and Use
Information Collection
Single Brides is the sole owner of the information collected on www.singlebrides.com. Single Brides collects information from our
users at several different points on our Web site. Registration In order to use this Web site, a user must first complete
the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use
this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to
complete the registration form, but encouraged so we can provide full service on our site.
Order
To complete a registration, we request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information
(such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). The
financial information is collected by iBill, which provides highly secure payment processing for www.singlebrides.com and
used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. Credit card information is encrypted using the SSL (Secure Sockets
Layer) protocol implemented by Netscape and Internet Explorer.
Information Use
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no
way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent
cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a
small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time.
Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control
over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.
Third Party Advertising
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by third party advertising partner. Information about user's visit
to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is
used to serve ads to users on this site. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.singlebrides.com only and
does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Log Files
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet
service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer
the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc.
are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use a tracking utility called [XXXX] that uses log files to analyze user
movement.
Communications from the Site
Special Offers and Updates
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information
on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not
receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.
Newsletter
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect
for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.
Service Announcements On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance,
if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these
communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.
Sharing
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we
have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal
process served on our Web site. Third Party Intermediaries We use an outside credit card processing company to bill
users for our services. This company do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary
purposes.
Choice/Opt-out
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications
by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at
.
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users
can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Single Brides, are not responsible for the privacy
practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements
of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to
information collected by this Web site.
Tell-A-Friend
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and
email address. Single Brides will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Single Brides
stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral
program. The friend may contact Single Brides at
to request the removal of this information from our database.
Security
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our user's information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web
site, their information is protected both online and off-line. When the registration order form asks users to enter
sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption
software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as an order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers
such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users
are just 'surfing'.
Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no
longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate user's personally identifiable information.
This can usually be done at the [member information page] or by emailing our Customer Support at [EMAIL ADDRESS]. [Or, contact
us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below].
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places
we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances,
if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:
Email:
Web site URL: http://www.singlebrides.com
Quick Search
I am:
Male
Between:
70
Country:
Join for free now
Gender:
Male
Female
Login name:
Password:
Confirm Password:
Email:
Important information
Members Login
Login name:
Password:
Forgot password?
Can't login?
1. POST
Post your unique profile and photos completely free.
2. BROWSE
Browse the profiles of thousands of singles for free.
3. CHAT
Chat live with your favorite singles. Get to know them before you meet them!
ASK ANNA
Everything you wanted to
know about online dating...
HomePrivacy policyAsk AnnaAll bridesAll menFAQContact us
Mail order brides at SingleBrides. Free marriage records, long-term dating relationships, love and marriage.© 2001-2020 SingleBrides.com. All rights reserved.
